<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HIMYM Moments</string>

    <string name="heading_title">HIMYM Moments</string>

<!--Title Items-->
    <string name="title_1">Legen — wait for it…</string>
    <string name="title_2">Odds of Love</string>
    <string name="title_3">After 2 a.m.</string>
    <string name="title_4">Mistakes</string>
    <string name="title_5">Be awesome!</string>
    <string name="title_6">Awesome cold</string>
    <string name="title_7">Understanding Barney</string>
    <string name="title_8">Steal an Orchestra?</string>
    <string name="title_9">Great Moments</string>
    <string name="title_10">As fast as she can</string>
    <string name="title_11">Designing Life</string>
    <string name="title_12">If not scared…</string>
    <string name="title_13">Lies</string>
    <string name="title_14">Stupid decisions</string>
    <string name="title_15">Baggage</string>
    <string name="title_16">Five Doppelgangers</string>
    <string name="title_17">Signs of the Universe</string>
    <string name="title_18">Gym?</string>

<!--Description items-->
    <string name="desc_1">It\'s going to be legen — wait for it — and I hope you\'re not lactose intolerant, because the second half of the word is — dary! Legendary!</string>
    <string name="desc_2">
        Look, I know the odds are the love of my life isn\'t going to magically
        walk through that door in a pumpkin costume at 2:43 in the morning.
        But it just seems as nice a spot as any to just, you know, sit and wait.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_3">
        When it\'s after 2 a.m. just go to sleep. Because the decisions you make after 2:00 a.m.
        are the wrong decisions.</string>
    <string name="desc_4">
        I know it\'s a mistake, but there are certain things in life where you know it\'s a mistake,
        but you don’t really know it\'s a mistake, because the only way to really know it\'s a mistake
        is to make the mistake, and look back and say, \'Yep, that was a mistake.\' So, really, the
        bigger mistake would be to not make the mistake because then you\'d go your whole life not
        really knowing if something is a mistake or not.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_5">When I get sad, I stop being sad and be awesome instead. True story.</string>
    <string name="desc_6">
        I\'m not sick. My nose is just overflowing with awesome and I had to get
        some of it out.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_7">
        When times are hard, it\'s impossible to keep him around. But when times are good, it\'s
        impossible to get rid of him.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_8">\'You stole a blue French Horn for me.\' \'I would have stolen you a whole orchestra.\'</string>
    <string name="desc_9">
        The great moments of your life won\'t necessarily be the things you do. They\'ll also be the things that happen to you. I\'m not saying you can\'t take action to
        affect the outcome of your life. You have to take action, and you will. But never forget that,
        on any day, you could step out the front door and your whole life can change forever.
        You see, the universe has a plan, kids, and that plan is always in motion. A butterfly flaps
        its wings and it starts to rain. It\'s a scary thought. But it\'s also kind of wonderful. All
        these little parts of the machine constantly working, making sure that you end up exactly
        where you\'re supposed to be, exactly when you\'re supposed to be there. The right place at
        the right time.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_10">
        I know that you are tired of waiting, and you may have to wait a little while more, but
        she\'s on her way, Ted. And she\'s getting here as fast as she can.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_11">Look, you can\'t design your life like a building. It doesn\'t work that
        way. You just have to live it, and it will design itself. Listen to what the world is
        telling you to do and take the leap.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_12">If you\'re not scared, then you\'re not taking a chance. If you\'re not
        taking a chance, then what the hell are you doing anyway?
    </string>
    <string name="desc_13">A lie is a great story that someone ruined with the truth.</string>
    <string name="desc_14">That\'s the thing about stupid decisions. We all make them.
        But time is funny. And sometimes a little magical. It can take a stupid decision and
        turn it into something else entirely.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_15">You see, everyone\'s got some baggage. It\'s part of life.
        But like anything else, it\'s easier when someone gives you a hand with.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_16">Look, we\'ve been all searching for the five doppelgangers, right?
        But eventually, over time, we all become our own doppelgangers. You know, these completely
        different people who just happen to look like us.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_17">You can ask the universe for signs all you want, but ultimately we’ll
        only see what we want to see… when we\'re ready to see it.
    </string>
    <string name="desc_18">I wound up shame-eating the whole pizza. I woke up all greasy and sweaty.
        My sheets looked like what they wrap deli sandwiches in. Maybe I should join a gym.
        Do you go to a gym?</string>


<!--Author names-->
    <string name="auth_1">~ Barney, S1 E03</string>
    <string name="auth_2">~ Ted, S1 E06</string>
    <string name="auth_3">~ Ted, S1 E18</string>
    <string name="auth_4">~ Lily, S1 E21</string>
    <string name="auth_5">~ Barney, S2 E01</string>
    <string name="auth_6">~ Barney, S2 E11</string>
    <string name="auth_7">~ Ted, S2 E19</string>
    <string name="auth_8">~ Robin and Ted, S2 E22</string>
    <string name="auth_9">~ Ted, S4 E22</string>
    <string name="auth_10">~ Stella, S4 E23</string>
    <string name="auth_11">~ Lily, S4 E24</string>
    <string name="auth_12">~ Ted, S5 E10</string>
    <string name="auth_13">~ Barney, S5 E19</string>
    <string name="auth_14">~ Ted, S5 E20</string>
    <string name="auth_15">~ Ted, S5 E23</string>
    <string name="auth_16">~ Ted, S5 E24</string>
    <string name="auth_17">~ Ted, S5 E24</string>
    <string name="auth_18">~ Ted, S3 E10</string>
</resources>